Stephen Jay Gould Papers, 1899-2004
Stanford University Libraries.
- Series 3. Manuscripts
  - Subseries 3. Articles, essays, and other writings by Gould
    - Exotic Interiors, annotated typescript (Box 469, Folder 4)
    - Faces are Special, photography by Rosamond Purcell, typescript (Box 469, Folder 5)
    - The Fascination of Dinosaurs, annotated typescript (Box 523, Folder 8)
    - Fifty Years of Interspecific Hybridization: Genetics and Morphometircs of a Controlled Experiment Involving the Land Snail in Florida by David S. Woodruff and Gould, typescript (Box 597, Folder 4)
    - First Man of the Earth, typescript and annotated galley (Box 469, Folder 6)
    - Flexibility for the Limits, typescript (Box 597, Folder 5)
    - Flexibility for the Limits, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 523, Folder 9)
    - Flowers of Glass, typescript (Box 469, Folder 7)
    - Flowers of Glass, typescript and galley proof (Box 597, Folder 6)
    - Footnotes, annotated typescript (Box 597, Folder 7)
    - Foreword to A Desert Calling: Life in a Forbidding Landscape (Box 597, Folder 8)
    - Foreword to the Third Edition from Five Kingdoms by Marguilis and Schwartz, typescript (Box 597, Folder 9)
    - Form + Scale in Nature + Culture, galley and correspondence (Box 469, Folder 8)
    - Freud's Joy in Simultaneous Subway Series, typescript and notes (Box 616, Folder 7)
    - From the Bitter Negro Pun to the Beautiful Breath Battle, manuscript (Box 597, Folder 10)
    - A Fruitful Meeting of Dinosaur Fiction and Science, typescript (Box 469, Folder 9)
    - Fulfilling the Spandrels of World and Mind, page proofs and typescript (Box 469, Folder 10)
    - Geology of New Providence Island, Bahamas by Garret and Gould, annotated typescript, correspondence and figures (2 folders)
    - [ The Geometer of Race], galley and typescript (Box 597, Folder 13)
    - Geometric Constraint and the Limited Fortunes of Reversal in a Maximally Snaillike Vermetid Gastropod by Gould and Robinson, annotated typescript (Box 597, Folder 14)
    - The Glory of His Time, And Ours, typescript (Box 469, Folder 11)
    - The Good People of Halifax, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 597, Folder 15)
    - The Great Asymetry, typescript and annotated galley (Box 688, Folder 3)
    - Gryphea by Gould and Hallam, annotated typescript, correspondence, figures and notes (Box 597, Folder 16)
    - Gulliver's Further Travels: The Necessity and Difficulty of a Hierarchical Theory of Selection, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 523, Folder 10)
    - Gulliver's further travels: the necessity and difficulty of a hierarchical theory of selection, galley (Box 482, Folder 8)
    - Heads or Tails (Box 469, Folder 12)
    - Healing Light and Legislative Heat, typescript (Box 482, Folder 9)
    - Healing Light and Legislative Heat, typescript (Box 616, Folder 8)
    - Healing Light and Legislative Heat, annotated typescript (Box 597, Folder 19)
    - The Hardening of the Modern Synthesis, typescript (Box 597, Folder 17)
    - The Hardest Narrative of All, typescript (Box 597, Folder 18)
    - Honoring a Great Career in Progress, typescript (Box 597, Folder 20)
    - How the Deer Got Its Hump, annotated typescript (Box 469, Folder 13)
    - How the Deer Got Its Hump, annotated typescript and annotated galley (Box 616, Folder 9)
    - How To Analyze Burgess Shale Disparity -- A Reply to Ridley, typescript (Box 469, Folder 14)
    - A Humane Galapagos, typescript, correspondence, and research (Box 482, Folder 10)
    - I Love a Parade, typescript (2 folders) (Box 597, Folder 21)
    - Impeaching a Self-Appointed Judge (a review of Darwin on Trial by Phillip E. Johnson), annotated typescript (Box 469, Folder 15)
    - The Individual in Darwin's World, galley and correspondence (Box 469, Folder 16)
    - Individuality, typescript (Box 597, Folder 22)
    - Individuality and adaptation across levels of selection by Gould and Elisabeth A. Lloyd, annotated galley and correspondence (Box 469, Folder 17)
    - The Inexorable Logic of the Punctuational Paradigm: Hugh de Vries on Species Selection, annotated typescript (Box 469, Folder 18)
    - Infiltration, typescript (Box 597, Folder 23)
    - Inside Dimensions, annotated typescript (Box 469, Folder 19)
    - The Interrelationship of Speciation and Punctuated Equilibrium, typescript, correspondence and notes (Box 469, Folder 20)
    - The Interrelationship of Speciation and Punctuated Equilibrium, typescript and correspondence (Box 616, Folder 10)
    - In the Company of Animals, partial annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 523, Folder 11)
    - Introduction, typescript (3 folders)
    - Introduction: A Lover's Quarrel, typescript (Box 469, Folder 24)
    - Introduction: The coherence of history, galley proof and annotated typescript (Box 598, Folder 1)
    - Introduction: The scales of contingency and punctuation in history, galley (Box 482, Folder 11)
    - Introduction to Cuvier Bibliography, typescript (Box 469, Folder 25)
    - Introduction to by David M. Raup, typescript (Box 469, Folder 26)
    - Introduction to Fate of the Mammoth by Claudine Cohen, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 598, Folder 3)
    - Introduction to by Niles Eldredge (Box 469, Folder 27)
    - Introduction to Shells Calendar, annotated typescript (Box 523, Folder 12)
    - Introduction to Shells Calendar, typescript, poem and correspondence (Box 598, Folder 2)
    - Introduction to Structure and Contingency, typescript and notes (Box 598, Folder 4)
    - Introduction to the Modern Library Science Series from Man's Place in Nature, galley and correspondence (Box 598, Folder 5)
    - [ Intro for Web Site], typescript (Box 616, Folder 11)
    - Is Uniformitarianism Necessary?, typescript (Box 598, Folder 6)
    - It Ain't Broke, typescript (Box 598, Folder 7)
    - It Ain't Broke, typescript and manuscript (Box 523, Folder 13)
    - The Joy and Necessity of Illustration, typescript (Box 598, Folder 8)
    - The Joy and Necessity of Illustration from The Art of Natural Geographic, typescript and correspondence (Box 482, Folder 12)
    - Kansas Becomes Oz, annotated typescript (Box 482, Folder 13)
    - Keynote Address for Social Research, annotated page proofs (Box 523, Folder 14)
    - La courbe en cloche du temps jadis joue les revenants, galley, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 598, Folder 9)
    - Ladders and Cones: Constraining Evolution by Canonical Icons, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 688, Folder 4)
    - Ladders and Cones: Contraining Evolution by Canonical Icons [from Hidden Histories of Science], annotated galley, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 598, Folder 10)
    - La grand galerie; preface, typescript (Box 469, Folder 28)
    - The Last Pennant Race, typescript (Box 469, Folder 29)
    - Layering, typescript and correspondence (Box 598, Folder 11)
    - Layering, annotated typescript and manuscript (Box 482, Folder 14)
    - Lecture 2, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 523, Folder 15)
    - Letter in reply to Sephardic Jew in King George's Court or The Anatomy Lesson, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 523, Folder 17)
    - Letter to Stephen Jay Gould to Donald Teeters: Reprinted by permission of writer and recipient, annotated typescript (Box 523, Folder 16)
    - Life in Punctuation, typescript (Box 598, Folder 12)
    - A Life's Drama, manuscript and annotated typescript (Box 598, Folder 13)
    - A Life's Epistolary Drama, typescript (Box 598, Folder 14)
    - Linking Belle Greene to Duchamp's Rule of Grammar, typescript (Box 598, Folder 15)
    - Lives For Our Watchful Waiting, typescript (Box 469, Folder 30)
    - Lives for Our Watchful Waiting, annotated typescript (Box 598, Folder 16)
    - Macroevolution from (The Oxford) Encyclopedia of Evolution, annotated typescript and annotated galley (Box 598, Folder 17)
    - Magic Places, typescript (Box 598, Folder 18)
    - The Microscope and the Mind, typescript (Box 470, Folder 1)
    - Millennial Madness, typescript (Box 598, Folder 19)
    - Millennial Madness, typescript and correspondence (Box 616, Folder 12)
    - Money: The Abstract Non-Sacred Cow, typescript (Box 598, Folder 20)
    - Money: The Abstract Non-Sacred Cow, annotated typescript and annotated galley (Box 523, Folder 18)
    - More Power to Him, typescript and correspondence (Box 598, Folder 21)
    - More Things in Heaven and Earth from In Coming to Life, typescript and correspondence (Box 523, Folder 19)
    - Natural History of Cerion XI. Genetics and Morphometrics of the Interaction Between Two Semispecies of Cerion (Pulmonata) on Abaco, Bahamas by David S. Woodruff and Gould, typescript, correspondence and figures (Box 598, Folder 22)
    - The Natural Status of Science as Literature, typescript (Box 470, Folder 2)
    - The Natural Status of Science as Literature, annotated typescript (Box 616, Folder 13)
    - Nature's Geometers, annotated typescript (Box 470, Folder 3)
    - Nature's Sweet Lore, annotated typescript (Box 598, Folder 23)
    - Non-Overlapping Magisteria, typescript (Box 599, Folder 1)
    - No Reversal of Fortune, typescript (Box 598, Folder 24)
    - No Reversal of Fortune, annotated typescript (Box 523, Folder 20)
    - No Science Without Fancy, No Art Without Facts, annotated typescript (Box 470, Folder 4)
    - No Science Without Fancy, No Art Without Facts: The Lepidoptery of Vladimir Nabokov, annotated galley (Box 482, Folder 15)
    - No Science Without Fancy, No Art Without Facts: The Lepidoptery of Vladimir Nabokov, proof and correspondence (Box 616, Folder 14)
    - Ode to Cecilia, annotated typescript (Box 599, Folder 2)
    - Of Coiled Oysters and Big Brains, annotated typescript (Box 470, Folder 5)
    - Of coiled oysters and big brains, annotated galley and correspondence (Box 523, Folder 21)
    - Of Coiled Oysters and Big Brains: How to Rescue theTerminology of Heterochrony, Now Gone Astray, annotated typescript (Box 599, Folder 3)
    - Of It, Not Above It, typescript (Box 470, Folder 6)
    - Of It, Not Above It, annotated typescript (Box 599, Folder 4)
    - On Mental and Visual Geometry, typescript (Box 599, Folder 7)
    - Of Mental and Visual Geometry, proof and correspondence (Box 523, Folder 22)
    - Of Tongue Worms, Velvet Worms and Water Bears, annotated typescript (Box 599, Folder 5)
    - The Old Red Sandstone, annotated typescript (Box 599, Folder 6)
    - On Genomenclature: A Comprehensible Taxonomy For Pseudogenes And Other by Jurgen Brosius and Gould, annotated typescript (Box 470, Folder 7)
    - On Telling, Altering, and Enriching Stories: An Unpublished Darwin Letter from a Key Incident in his Later Life, annotated typescript (Box 470, Folder 9)
    - On Telling, Altering, and Enriching Stories: An unpublished Darwin Letter from a Key Incident in his Later Life, annotated typescript, notes and research materials (Box 599, Folder 8)
    - On Telling, Altering and Enriching Stories: An unpublished Darwin Letter from a Key Incident in his Later Life, Chapter 17 in Evolutinary Paleobiology, edited by Jablonski, annotated typescript (Box 599, Folder 9)
    - On the Goals and Limits of Evolutionary Psychology: A Critique of Anderson, annotated typescript (Box 470, Folder 8)
    - On the Goals and Limits of Evolutionary Psychology: A Critique of Anderson by Gould and Koslyn, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 599, Folder 10)
    - On Transmuting Boyle's Law to Darwin's Revolution, typescript (Box 470, Folder 10)
    - On Transmuting Boyle's Law to Darwin's Revolution, annotated proof (Box 616, Folder 15)
    - One Hundred Years from Now, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 523, Folder 23)
    - Only Human, article and correspondence (Box 524, Folder 1)
    - Ontogeny + Phylogeny - Revisited, annotated typescript (Box 470, Folder 11)
    - Ontogeny and Phylogeny - Revisited and Reunited, typescript (Box 599, Folder 11)
    - Ontogeny and Phylogeny - Revisited and Reunited, annotated article and correspondence (Box 470, Folder 12)
    - Our Kingdom For A Replicate, annotated typescript (Box 470, Folder 13)
    - Our Kingdom for a Replicate, annotated typescript (Box 599, Folder 12)
    - Out of Time in the Dreaming Jungles, typescript (Box 470, Folder 14)
    - Paleontology and Chronology of Two Evolutionary Transitions by Hybridization in the Bahamian Land Snail by Glenn A. Goodfriend and Gould, typescript (Box 470, Folder 15)
    - Paleontology and Chronology of Two Evolutionary Transitions by Hybridization in the Bahamian Land Snail by Gleen A. Goodfriend and Gould, typescript and figures (Box 599, Folder 14)
    - Paleontology and Chronology of Two Evolutionary Transitions by Hybridization in the Bahamian Land Snail by Gleen A. Goodfriend and Gould, proofs (Box 599, Folder 13)
    - Panglossian Paradigm (French translation), annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 599, Folder 15)
    - The paradox of genius, annotated galley and correspondence (Box 470, Folder 16)
    - The Paradox of the Visibly Irrelevant, annotated typescript (Box 599, Folder 16)
    - The Phenomenon of Medawar, typescript (Box 470, Folder 17)
    - Placid in Plaster, annotated typescript (Box 599, Folder 17)
    - A Planetary Scale for the 70's, annotated typescript (Box 470, Folder 18)
    - A Planetary Scale for the 70s, galley and correspondence (Box 599, Folder 18)
    - A Plea and a Hope for Martian Paleontology, annotated typescript (Box 470, Folder 19)
    - Position Statement: 1998 Council on Ideas, annotated typescript (Box 482, Folder 16)
    - The Positive Power of Skepticism - Foreword to Why People Believe Weird Things by Michael Shermer, annotated typescript (Box 599, Folder 19)
    - The Pre-Adamite In A Nutshell, typescript (Box 470, Folder 20)
    - Precis for a Baseball Book, typescript (Box 599, Folder 20)
    - Precis for a lecture on Creativity in Evolution and Human Innovation, typescript (Box 470, Folder 21)
    - Predicting: The Biggest Millennial Fallacy, typescript (Box 470, Folder 22)
    - Preface, typescript
    - Preface, typescript (Box 600, Folder 1)
    - Preface, typescript (2 folders)
    - Preface, annotated typescript (Box 599, Folder 21)
    - Preface, typescript and correspondence (Box 600, Folder 2)
    - Preface--1998 Shell Calendar, annotated typescript (Box 600, Folder 3)
    - "Preface to Anne Rogovin's Learning by Doing," annotated typescript (Box 600, Folder 6)
    - Preface to Mares, annotated typescript (Box 616, Folder 16)
    - Preface to, typescript (Box 600, Folder 7)
    - Preposterous, typescript (Box 616, Folder 17)
    - Preposterous by Gould and Rosamond Purcell, typescript (Box 470, Folder 26)
    - Prolonged Stability in Local Populations of (Pleistocene-Recent) on Great Bahama Bank, typescript (Box 470, Folder 27)
    - The promotion and prevention of recoiling in a maximally snaillike vermetid gastropod by Gould and Betsey A. Robinson, typescript (Box 470, Folder 28)
    - A Proper Darwinian Gentleman at Marx's Funeral: The Oddest Couple of Evolution and Revolution, annotated typescript (Box 482, Folder 17)
    - Prophet for the Earth (a review of Edward O. Wilson's The Diversity of Life), typescript (Box 470, Folder 29)
    - Proposal For a Highly Informative and Somewhat Offbeat Book on a Great Subject in a Currently Crowded Field: The Millennium, typescript (Box 471, Folder 1)
    - Pulling Teeth, annotated typescript (Box 524, Folder 2)
    - Punctuated Equilibrium, by Gould and Godfray (Box 616, Folder 18)
    - Punctuated Equilibrium as a basis for Macroevolutionary Theory (Box 600, Folder 8)
    - Queerer Than We Can Suppose: The Major Features of Life's Pathways, annotated typescript (Box 471, Folder 2)
    - Radiolaria, annotated galley (Box 600, Folder 9)
    - Random Sox, typescript (Box 471, Folder 3)
    - The Real Error of Cyril Burt: Factor Analysis and the Reification of Intelligence, partial annotated typescript (Box 600, Folder 10)
    - Reality Strangles Invention, annotated typescript (Box 600, Folder 11)
    - Reconstructing (And Deconstructing) The Past, annotated typescript (Box 471, Folder 4)
    - Recovering Bacon's Paradox, typescript (Box 471, Folder 5)
    - Redrafting the Tree of Life (Box 600, Folder 12)
    - Redrafting the Tree of Life, annotated typescript (Box 471, Folder 6)
    - Redrafting the Tree of Life, annotated typescript (Box 524, Folder 3)
    - Redrafting the Tree of Life, annotated typescript, figures and notes (Box 600, Folder 13)
    - Reflections on 'Popular Academics', typescript (Box 616, Folder 19)
    - Reply, typescript (Box 471, Folder 7)
    - Reply to Dennett and Wright, typescript (Box 600, Folder 14)
    - Report to the Librarian, annotated typescript (Box 524, Folder 4)
    - Report to the Librarian, annotated typescript (Box 600, Folder 15)
    - Report to the Librarian by Gould and Rosamond Purcell, typescript (Box 471, Folder 8)
    - Requiem Eternal, typescript (Box 600, Folder 16)
    - Research at the Smithsonian, typescript (Box 471, Folder 9)
    - "Review of Adrian Desmond, Huxley: Evolution's High Priest," typescript (Box 600, Folder 17)
    - "Review of African Silences by Peter Matthiessen," typescript (Box 471, Folder 10)
    - Review of, by Thomas Laqueur, typescript and annotated galley (Box 471, Folder 11)
    - "Review of ORIGINS Reconsidered by Richard Leakey and Roger Lewin," typescript (Box 471, Folder 12)
    - Review of 'Principles of Geology,' first edition, volume 1, by Charles Lyell, annotated typescript (Box 471, Folder 13)
    - A review of: by Helena Cronin...with comments on by Niles Eldredge...and by Peter D. Ward, annotated typescript (Box 471, Folder 14)
    - Room of One's Own, typescript (Box 600, Folder 18)
    - Rough Injustice, typescript and correspondence (Box 600, Folder 19)
    - Running Head Introduction (Box 471, Folder 15)
    - Scales of Change, typescript (Box 600, Folder 20)
    - Scales of Change from Forces of Change, annotated typescript, correspondence, and proofs (Box 600, Folder 22)
    - Scales of Change from Forces of Change: A New View of Nature, annotated typescript (Box 482, Folder 18)
    - The Scales of Contingency and Punctuation in History, typescript (Box 600, Folder 23)
    - Scales of Destruction, photography by Rosamond Purcell, typescript (Box 471, Folder 16)
    - Scales of Time, typescript and correspondence (Box 600, Folder 24)
    - Scales of Time, annotated typescript (Box 481, Folder 6)
    - Science literacy for the twenty-first century, promotional material (Box 600, Folder 25)
    - A Seahorse for all Races, annotated typescript (Box 600, Folder 21)
    - Self-Help for a Hedgehog Stuck on a Molehill, typescript (Box 524, Folder 5)
    - Self-Help for a Hedgehog Stuck on a Molehill, typescript (Box 600, Folder 27)
    - Sex, Drugs, Disasters, and the Extinction of Dinosaurs, typescript and correspondence (Box 600, Folder 28)
    - The Shape of Life, annotated typescript (Box 471, Folder 17)
    - The Shape of Life, galley and annotated typescript (Box 600, Folder 29)
    - Size Matters and Function Counts, Prologue to Evolutionary Anatomy of the Primate Cerebral Cortex, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 601, Folder 1)
    - The Smoking Gun of Eugenics, typescript (Box 471, Folder 18)
    - The Soul of a City (Box 601, Folder 2)
    - The Soul of a City, or Changing Faces in Wondrous Places, typescript (Box 471, Folder 19)
    - Speaking of Snails + Scales, annotated typescript (Box 601, Folder 3)
    - Speciation and Punctuated Equilibria, by Niles Eldredge and Gould, typescript (Box 616, Folder 20)
    - Species Selection on Variability by Elisabeth A. Lloyd and Gould, annotated typescript and galley (Box 471, Folder 20)
    - Statement in Support of S.58, the National Biological Diversity Conservation and Environmental Research Act, typescript (Box 471, Folder 21)
    - Statement in Support of S.58, the National Biological Diversity Conservation and Environmental Research Act, typescript (Box 601, Folder 4)
    - Statement on Charles Marshall, annotated typescript (Box 524, Folder 6)
    - Stem Cells and the Great Paradox of Embryology, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 601, Folder 5)
    - Still a Majority: Reply to Levinton and Clarke, typescript (Box 471, Folder 22)
    - Still the Greatest, typescript and correspondence (Box 601, Folder 6)
    - Strange Adventure, typescript, correspondence and research (Box 524, Folder 7)
    - Strange Adventure, proofs and correspondence (Box 601, Folder 7)
    - Structural Laws as Constraints and Opportunities in Science and Art, typescript (Box 471, Folder 23)
    - Structural Laws as Constraints and Opportunities in Science and Art, annotated typescript (Box 601, Folder 8)
    - The Substantial Ghost: Toward a General Explanation of Duchamp's Artful Wordplays, annotated typescript (Box 524, Folder 8)
    - Sultan of Sentimentality, typescript (Box 471, Folder 24)
    - Systematics and Levels of Covariation in Cerion from the Turks and Caicos Islands, annotated typescript, data and research (Box 471, Folder 25)
    - A Tale of Two Heroes, typescript (Box 601, Folder 10)
    - A Tale of Two Heroes, annotated typescript (Box 524, Folder 9)
    - A Task for Paleobiology at the Threshold of Majority, typescript (Box 601, Folder 9)
    - A Task for Paleobiology at the Threshold of Majority, typescript (Box 471, Folder 26)
    - A Taxonomist's Taxonomist, annotated typescript and research (Box 601, Folder 11)
    - The Taxonomy and Geographic Variation of on San Salvador (Bahama Islands), typescript and figures (Box 471, Folder 27)
    - Technical Comment, annotated typescript (Box 524, Folder 10)
    - The Teleological Myth, annotated typescript (Box 481, Folder 7)
    - Tempo and Mode in Macroevolutionary Reconstruction of Darwinism, test galley and correspondence (Box 472, Folder 1)
    - Tempo and Mode in the Moacroevolutionary Reconstruction of Darwinism, galley proof (Box 688, Folder 5)
    - Ten Millennial Mileposts in Understanding the History of Life, typescript (Box 601, Folder 12)
    - Ten Millennial Mileposts in Understanding the History of Life, annotated typescript (Box 616, Folder 21)
    - A Testimony, typescript (Box 472, Folder 2)
    - A Testimony, typescript (Box 601, Folder 13)
    - Theory of the Living Earth, annotated clipping (Box 616, Folder 22)
    - They Also Serve..., typescript (Box 472, Folder 4)
    - This Was A Man, typescript (Box 472, Folder 3)
    - Three Facets of Evolution, annotated typescript (Box 601, Folder 15)
    - Thinking about Evolution, correspondence (Box 601, Folder 14)
    - Three Facets of Evolution, typescript (Box 472, Folder 5)
    - Timescales of Evolution, final layout (Box 601, Folder 16)
    - To Open A Millennium, annotated typescript (Box 601, Folder 17)
    - To Open a Millennium from The Best American Essays, 2002 (Box 481, Folder 8)
    - To Open A Millennium from Best American Essays 2002, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 524, Folder 11)
    - To President Jacques Delors, annotated typescript and correspondence (Box 472, Folder 6)
    - Tragic Optimism for a Millennial Dawning (Box 472, Folder 7)
    - Tragic Optimism for a Millennial Dawning, annotated typescript (Box 481, Folder 9)
    - Transform or Perish, typescript (Box 472, Folder 8)
    - Triumph of the Root-Heads, annotated typescript (Box 601, Folder 18)
    - The True Embodiment of Everything That's Excellent: The Strange Adventure of Gilbert and Sullivan, annotated proofs and correspondence (Box 601, Folder 19)
    - The Truth of Fiction, typescript and correspondence (Box 472, Folder 9)
    - The Truth of Fiction: An Exegesis of G. G. Simpson's Dinosaur Fantasy, annotated typescript (Box 601, Folder 20)